[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Napoleon Dynamite, Pedro is Napoleon\u2019s best friend. What was Pedros last name?", "correct_answer": "Sanchez", "incorrect_answers": ["Rodriguez", "It is never mentioned", "Gonzales"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Armageddon, the character played by Ben Affleck takes the place of Harry S. Stamper, portrayed by Bruce Willis and detonates the bomb that splits the asteroid in two.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is an example of underpromotion in chess?", "correct_answer": "Converting your pawn into a knight", "incorrect_answers": ["Giving your opponent knight odds", "Telling your opponent you are a duffer when you are really an expert", "Taking your opponents pawn with your knight instead of your queen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What role did Jack Black play in the comedy film Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy?", "correct_answer": "Motorcyclist", "incorrect_answers": ["An extra on the set", "Police Man", "Rival Anchorman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following words were spoken by Leo, referring to Jin, in which movie?\nI sacrificed three years for you. How could you love him after only three days?", "correct_answer": "House of Flying Daggers", "incorrect_answers": ["Tempting Heart", "Returner", "Kiss of the Dragon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the original drummer for the Beatles.", "correct_answer": "Pete Best", "incorrect_answers": ["Brian Epstein", "Richard Starkey", "Stu Sutcliffe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Jet Lis characters name in the movie Hero, directed by Zhang Yimou?", "correct_answer": "Nameless", "incorrect_answers": ["Broken Sword", "Sky", "Flying Snow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not an actual breed of horse?", "correct_answer": "Sioux", "incorrect_answers": ["Russian Trotter", "Belgian", "Murgese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do wolves have a social structure?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the name Stegosaurus?", "correct_answer": "Roof Lizard", "incorrect_answers": ["Tank Lizard", "Spike Lizard", "Spike Tail"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the villains henchman, in the movie The Man with the Golden Gun?", "correct_answer": "Nick Nack", "incorrect_answers": ["Riff Raff", "Ding Dong", "Bee Boom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This former member of Monty Python provided the voice of Merlin in the 2007 movie Shrek the Third.", "correct_answer": "Eric Idle", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Palin", "Terry Gilliam", "John Cleese"]}]